RG 005:034, Office of the Governor: John Dempsey (1961-1971)
Connecticut State Library
- Series 11. Speeches with related materials, 1961-1970
  - Large type copies, 1961-1969
    - Democratic Affairs (Box A-431)
      - West Hartford Democratic Town Committee Rally, 1966 September 26 (Box A-431)
      - Windham County Democratic Association, Annual Dinner Meeting, Plainfield, 1966 May 28 (Box A-431)
      - Young Democratic Clubs of Conn., Annual Convention, Danbury, 1966 April 29 (Box A-431)
    - Economy of State (Box A-431)
      - Conn. Bankers Association, Hartford, 1966 January 19 (Box A-431)
      - Conference on Research and Economic Growth, Conn. Research Commission, Westport, 1966 December 8 (Box A-431)
      - Temple Israel, Men's Club, Westport, 1966 April 19 (Box A-431)
    - Education (Box A-432)
      - American Welding Society (Box A-432)
      - Middlesex Community College (Box A-432)
      - National Science Teachers (Box A-432)
    - Elderly (Box A-432)
      - Conference on Economic Opportunities for Connecticut's Older Citizens (Box A-432)
      - Conn. Council of Senior Citizens, Bridgeport, 1966 October 26 (Box A-432)
      - Conn. Council of Senior Citizens, Lake Compounce, Bristol, 1966 June 21 (Box A-432)
    - Elderly Housing (Box A-432)
      - Manchester - West Hill Gardens Edition - Housing for the Elderly, 1966 September 10 (Box A-432)
      - New Haven Crawford Manor (Housing for the Elderly), 1966 September 9 (Box A-432)
      - Dedication - Pine Tree Apartments, Fairfield, 1967 October 14 (Box A-432)
      - Putnam - Johnston (Dr. Robert) - Housing Development for the Elderly, 1966 May 17 (Box A-432)
      - Waterbury - Dedication of Franklin D. Roosevelt Apartments (For the Elderly), 1966 October 26 (Box A-432)
    - Equal Employment Opportunity (Box A-432)
      - Conn. Town Council for Equal Employment Opportunity, Hartford, 1966 December 6 (Box A-432)
      - Conn. Council on Equal Employment Opportunity - Greater Hartford Chairman of Committee, Hartford, 1966 February 11 (Box A-432)
      - Council for Equal Employment Opportunity, Hartford - Bridgeport, 1966 May 5-6 (Box A-432)
    - Federal-State Relations (Box A-432)
      - Community Conference on Federal Aid for Cities and Towns, 1966 February 15 (Box A-432)
      - Federal-State Conference at State Capitol, 1967 June 1 (Box A-432)
    - General (Box A-432)
      - American Chambers of Commerce - Executive Management Conference, Hartford, 1966 October 10 (Box A-432)
      - Arts, Commission on the, Conference, Hall of the House, 1966 June 27 (Box A-432)
      - Association of Investment Brokers Annual Dinner, 1967 September 7 (Box A-432)
      - Boy Scouts of America Region 1 - West Harwich, 1967 November 7 (Box A-432)
      - Kick-off Dinner, Boy Scouts Expansion Program, Hartford, 1967 November 7 (Box A-432)
      - Dedication - Community Services Building, New Haven, 1967 October 29 (Box A-432)
      - Conn. Bar Association, 91st Annual Meeting, 1966 October 18 (Box A-432)
      - Conn. Council on Crime & Delinquency, Bloomfield, 1966 September 21 (Box A-432)
      - Council 16 - Annual Convention, 1967 October 26 (Box A-432)
      - Conn. Library Association - Annual Meeting, Hartford, 1967 March 28 (Box A-432)
      - Conn. Public Expenditures Council, Annual Meeting, Hartford, 1966 May 10 (Box A-432)
      - Conn. State Labor Council - Annual Convention, 1967 September 15 (Box A-432)
      - Conn. State Safety Commission - Awards Meeting, 1967 September 25 (Box A-432)
      - Conn. Valley Hospital 100th Anniversary, Middletown, 1967 October 3 (Box A-432)
      - Correction, Dept. of, Statement of Gov. Dempsey Signing of P.A. 152, 1967 May 25 (Box A-432)
      - Fairfield Preparatory School 25th Anniversary, 1967 September 12 (Box A-432)
      - First Company, Governor's Foot Guard - 196th Anniversary, 1967 September 30 (Box A-432)
      - Governor's Foot Guard, First Company, Hartford, 1966 October 1 (Box A-432)
      - Governor's Horse Guard, First Company, 1966 September 10 (Box A-432)
      - Governor's Prayer Breakfast, 6th Annual, Hartford, 1967 March 22 (Box A-432)
      - Hamden Chamber of Commerce, Annual Meeting, 1967 March 1 (Box A-432)
      - Hartford National Bank & Trust Co. Dedication (Box A-432)
      - Italian Immigration, American Committee on, Annual Dinner, Hamden, 1966 May 9 (Box A-432)
      - Memorial Service, Capitol Rotunda, 1967 May 26 (Box A-432)
      - Memorial Service, Conn. State Employees, Post 6041, VFW, Hartford, 1966 May 26 (Box A-432)
      - National Order of Women Legislators, 29th Convention, 1967 October 10 (Box A-432)
      - New England Associated Press News Executives Association, 1966 October 6 (Box A-432)
      - New England Press Association, Boston, 1966 January 21 (Box A-432)
      - Plymouth - Dedication of Hancock Brook and Northfield Brooks Dam, Hancock Brook, 1966 October 21 (Box A-432)
      - Putnam - Police and Fire Building, Formal Opening, 1966 September 23 (Box A-432)
      - Real Estate Boards Annual Convention, 1967 September 25 (Box A-432)
      - Research and Economic Growth Conference, Avon, 1966 September 12 (Box A-432)
      - Rotary Club of Danbury, 1966 October 5 (Box A-432)
      - State Employees Freedom Bond Campaign, 1967 September 12 (Box A-432)
    - Highway Safety (Box A-432)
      - Governor's Traffic Safety Conference, Central Conn. State College, New Britain, 1966 April 23 (Box A-432)
      - Governor's Youth Traffic Safety Conference, New Britain, 1967 October 27 (Box A-432)
      - Governor's Youth Traffic Safety Conference, New Haven, 1966 October 28 (Box A-432)
    - Highways (Box A-432)
      - Bridgeport - Ground Breaking Route 25, 1966 July 26 (Box A-432)
      - Groton - Opening of Access Highway, 1966 November 3 (Box A-432)
      - Interstate Highway 91 (New Haven to Meriden), 1966 January 6 (Box A-432)
      - Torrington, Route 8, Dedication of 3 - 1/3 Section, 1969 July 19 (Box A-432)
      - Route 8 - Interstate 84 Interchange, Waterbury, 1967 October 27 (Box A-432)
      - Waterbury - Opening of Sectior3 of Route 8 and I-84, 1967 October 26 (Box A-432)
    - Housing (Box A-432)
      - Conn. Association of Real Estate Boards, Hartford, 1966 October 13 (Box A-432)
    - Industry (Box A-432)
      - Aerosol Techniquest, Inc., 1966 October 8 (Box A-432)
      - Aerotherm Plant, Dedication of, Bantam, 1966 February 4 (Box A-432)
      - Baldwin-Gegenheimer Corporation, Stamford, Opening Ceremonies, 1966 June 3 (Box A-432)
      - Baltimore Business Forms, Inc. Opening Ceremonies, Winsted, 1966 July 29 (Box A-432)
      - Conn. Yankee Atomic Power Co. Plant Dedication, 1967 October 12 (Box A-432)
      - Conn. Industrial Development Council, Greenwich, 1966 June 6 (Box A-432)
      - Danco Plant, Dedication of, Putnam, 1966 September 23 (Box A-432)
      - General Time Corporation, Industrial Controls Division, Plant Dedication, Torrington, 1967 April 12 (Box A-432)
      - Knox Glass, Inc., Opening of New Plant, Danielson, 1966 September 30 (Box A-432)
      - Manufacturers Association of Conn., 151st Annual Meeting, Yale University, 1966 September 8 (Box A-432)
      - Risom, Jens Design, Inc. National Sales Meeting, North Grosvenor Dale, 1966 March 28 (Box A-432)
      - Savings Bank Life Insurance Company, Hartford Club, 1966 June 16 (Box A-432)
      - Southeastern Conn. Chamber of Commerce Industrial Sites Tour for New York and Bos. Brokers, 1966 May 18 (Box A-432)
      - Winchester-Western Centennial Dinner, 1966 June 30 (Box A-432)
    - Mental Health (Box A-432)
      - Mental Health Center, New Haven, 1966 September 30 (Box A-432)
    - Mental Retardation (Box A-432)
      - Greater Hartford Center for the Retarded, Newington, 1966 September 14 (Box A-432)
      - Mental Retardation Planning, Committee on, Senate Chamber, Hartford, 1966 April 27 (Box A-432)
      - New Haven Regional Center for the Mentally Retarded, 1966 January 28 (Box A-432)
      - United Automobile Workers Citizenship Council, Waverly Inn, Cheshire, 1966 June 14 (Box A-433)
    - New Haven Railroad (Box A-433)
      - Catholic Club of Norwalk, Lincoln Day Banquet, 1966 February 10 (Box A-433)
      - Conn. Transportation Authority, Meeting, Senate Chambers, State Capitol, 1966 July 25 (Box A-433)
      - New Haven Railroad Meeting, Greenwich, Statements of Gov. Dempsey, 1966 September 27 (Box A-433)
      - Statement of Gov. Dempsey at Meeting of Governors, Washington, D.C., 1967 March 21 (Box A-433)
    - Recreation (Box A-433)
      - Governor's Conference on Recreation, Hartford Hilton, 1967 November 1 (Box A-433)
      - Governor's Conference on Recreation, 7th Annual, Hartford, 1966 October 20 (Box A-433)
    - Regional Planning (Box A-433)
      - New Britain Chamber of Commerce, 1966 May 10 (Box A-433)
      - New England Council Seminar of New England's Economic Dev. Trends, 1966 April 10 (Box A-433)
      - Rockville Area Chamber of Commerce, 1966 March 30 (Box A-433)
      - Southington-Plainville-Bristol Industrial Management Club, 1966 January 13 (Box A-433)
      - Wallingford Chamber of Commerce, Annual Membership Meeting, 1966 May 26 (Box A-433)
    - Rehabilitation (Box A-433)
      - Good Will Industries of Conn., 1966 May 6 (Box A-433)
      - New London Service Clubs, 1966 October 18 (Box A-433)
    - Safety (Miscellaneous) (Box A-433)
      - Northeastern States Boating Administrators Conference, Groton, 1966 May 18 (Box A-433)
  - Background material for speeches, 1961-1970
    Alphabetical by subject.
    - Agriculture (Box A-434)
    - Alcohol (Box A-434)
    - C. Bowles (Box A-434)
    - Brotherhood (Box A-434)
    - Civil Rights (Box A-434)
    - Commencement (Box A-434)
    - Conn. Livability (Box A-434)
    - Conservation (Box A-434)
    - County Government (Box A-434)
    - Development (Box A-434)
    - Education (Box A-434)
    - Federal Education Program 1957 (Box A-434)
    - Elderly (Box A-434)
    - Elections - Getting out the Vote (Box A-434)
    - Foreign Policy (Box A-434)
    - General (Box A-434)
    - General (Box A-434)
    - Genesis (Box A-434)
    - German Reunification (Box A-434)
    - Good Ideas, Thoughts (Box A-434)
    - Good Government (Box A-434)
    - Governor's Job (Box A-434)
    - Highway (Box A-434)
    - Industrial Development (Box A-434)
    - Industry (Box A-434)
    - Italians (Box A-434)
    - Jackson Speech: Free Men Against Time (Box A-434)
    - Jewish (Box A-434)
    - Kiwannis (Box A-434)
    - Leadership (Box A-434)
    - Liberalism (Box A-434)
    - Lincoln (Box A-434)
    - Little Rock and the Muscovite Moon (Box A-434)
    - Mental Health (Box A-434)
    - Speech by Edward R. Murrow before Columbia University Scholastic Press Association (Box A-434)
    - New Britain (Box A-434)
    - Norwich Rose Festival (Box A-434)
    - Polish Millennium (Box A-434)
    - Politics (Box A-434)
    - Pollution (Box A-434)
    - Quotations (Box A-434)
    - Religious Quotations (Box A-434)
    - Regional Planning (Box A-434)
    - St. Lucy (Box A-434)
    - Scholarship (Box A-434)
    - Service Clubs (Box A-434)
    - St. Patrick's Day (Box A-434)
    - Trinity Convocation Booklet (Box A-434)
    - University of Hartford (Box A-434)
    - Urban Renewal (Box A-434)
    - Veterans (Box A-434)
    - Vocational-Technical (Box A-434)
    - Washington-Lincoln (Box A-434)
    - Water Resources (Box A-434)
    - Welfare (Box A-434)
    - Youth (Box A-434)
  - Large type copied marked for reading, 1961-1970
    - Aerotherm Division of Universal Oil Products Co., Groundbreaking, Bantam, 1965 June 23 (Box Volume 1 (A-435))
    - Albertus Magnus College, Commencement Exercises, New Haven, 1962 June 7 (Box Volume 1 (A-435))
    - American Federation of State, County & Municipal Employees, Hartford, 1961 September 22 (Box Volume 1 (A-435))
    - American Federation of State, County & Municipal Employees, Hartford, 1961 September 14 (Box Volume 1 (A-435))
    - American Federation of State, County & Municipal Employees, Hartford, 1965 October 1 (Box Volume 1 (A-435))
    - Anaconda American Brass Co., delivered by Graham Treadway, Waterbury, 1961 September 21 (Box Volume 1 (A-435))
    - Annhurst College, Commencement, South Woodstock, 1964 May 31 (Box Volume 1 (A-435))
    - Apprenticeship Council Conference, State Capitol, Hartford, 1962 September 24 (Box Volume 1 (A-435))
    - Arnold Bakers, Greenwich, 1964 September 18 (Box Volume 1 (A-435))
    - Arnold College, Alumni Reunion, University of Bridgeport, Bridgeport, 1962 April 28 (Box Volume 1 (A-435))
    - Association Press, Annual Meeting, Connecticut Circuit, Bristol, 1961 May 11 (Box Volume 1 (A-435))
    - Asylum Hill Congregational Church, Hartford, 1965 May 21 (Box Volume 1 (A-435))
    - Automotive Trades Association, Connecticut, Hartford, 1961 November 14 (Box Volume 1 (A-435))
    - Bar Association, Connecticut, Hartford, 1965 October 19 (Box Volume 1 (A-435))
    - Bear Path Elementary School, Dedication Exercises, Hamden, 1962 October 10 (Box Volume 1 (A-435))
    - Benrus Company Plant, Ridgefield, 1964 August 4 (Box Volume 1 (A-435))
    - Beth-El Religious School, Dedication, Waterbury, 1962 June 18 (Box Volume 1 (A-435))
    - Bethel A.M.E. Church, Hartford, 1962 March 18 (Box Volume 1 (A-435))
    - Birdie Missile Site, Dedication, Cromwell, 1962 March 13 (Box Volume 1 (A-435))
    - Blind, Connecticut Institute for the, Hartford, 1965 October 7 (Box Volume 1 (A-435))
    - Bloomfield Town Hall, Dedication, 1962 March 4 (Box Volume 1 (A-435))
    - B'nai B'rith, Connecticut Valley Council, Monticello, New York, 1964 April 25 (Box Volume 1 (A-435))
    - Boy Scouts of America, Eastern Connecticut Council, University of Connecticut, Storrs, 1965 April 9 (Box Volume 1 (A-435))
    - Boy Scouts, Annual Scouters' Banquet, Hartford, 1965 April 24 (Box Volume 1 (A-435))
    - Bridgeport Chamber of Commerce, 1961 November 20 (Box Volume 1 (A-435))
    - Bridgeport Engineering Institute, Commencement Address, 1961 October 22 (Box Volume 1 (A-435))
    - Bridgeport Traffic Association, 1962 January 11 (Box Volume 1 (A-435))
    - Bristol Chamber of Commerce, 1962 January 9 (Box Volume 1 (A-435))
    - Brotherhood Homes, Dedication Ceremonies, Hartford, 1961 October 29 (Box Volume 1 (A-435))
    - Bullard-Havens School, Commencement, Bridgeport, 1962 June 9 (Box Volume 1 (A-435))
    - Catholic Charities, Annual Dinner Meeting of Advisory Board, Norwich, 1961 May 7 (Box Volume 2 (A-436))
    - Catholic Youth Organization (CYO), First Annual Archdiocesan Convention, West Hartford, 1964 October 31 (Box Volume 2 (A-436))
    - Central Connecticut State College, New Britain, 1962 May 12 (Box Volume 2 (A-436))
    - Channel 3 (Governor's Committee) Hall of the House, Hartford, 1961 September 18 (Box Volume 2 (A-436))
    - Channel 3, Statement before Commission on Interstate & Foreign Commerce, House of Representatives, Washington, D.C., 1962 March 7 (Box Volume 2 (A-436))
    - Chemical Industry Day, Hartford, 1965 April 26 (Box Volume 2 (A-436))
    - Chicago Speech (Detroit-Chicago trip), 1962 May 17 (Box Volume 2 (A-436))
    - Citizenship, New Britain Council on Annual Citizenship Day, 1964 September 13 (Box Volume 2 (A-436))
    - Civil Defense, Operation Alert, 1961 April 29 (Box Volume 2 (A-436))
    - Civil Defense, Conference State Capitol, 1961 November 15 (Box Volume 2 (A-436))
    - Civil Defense Meeting, State Capitol, 1963 January 3 (Box Volume 2 (A-436))
    - Civil Rights Commission, 20th Anniversary, Wallingford, 1963 October 24 (Box Volume 2 (A-436))
    - Civil Rights Rally, State Capitol, 1965 May 26 (Box Volume 2 (A-436))
    - Civil War Centennial Commission Celebration, Guilford, 1965 June 26 (Box Volume 2 (A-436))
    - Clean Water Task Force, Organization Meeting, State Capitol, 1965 October 18 (Box Volume 2 (A-436))
    - Connecticut Agricultural Experiment Station, Field Day, Hamden, 1961 August 9 (Box Volume 2 (A-436))
    - Connecticut Association for Health, Physical Education and Recreation, Hartford, 1962 October 26 (Box Volume 2 (A-436))
    - Connecticut Building Congress Exposition & Symposium, Hartford, 1961 March 28 (Box Volume 2 (A-436))
    - Connecticut Building Congress, Cheshire, 1962 October 25 (Box Volume 2 (A-436))
    - Connecticut Development Commission Conference, New York, 1963 November 8 (Box Volume 2 (A-436))
    - Connecticut Industrial Development Council, Industrial Tour, Cheshire, 1961 May 24 (Box Volume 2 (A-436))
    - Connecticut Industrial Development Council, Industrial Tour, Windsor, 1963 May 14 (Box Volume 2 (A-436))
    - Connecticut Milk Producers Association, Hartford, 1961 March 14 (Box Volume 2 (A-436))
    - Connecticut National Guard, Nike-Ajax Missile Sites, State Armory, Hartford, 1961 February 12 (Box Volume 2 (A-436))
    - Connecticut Public Expenditure Council, Hartford, 1961 May 23 (Box Volume 2 (A-436))
    - Connecticut Public Expenditure Council, 1962 May 22 (Box Volume 2 (A-436))
    - Connecticut Public Expenditure Council, 1963 May 22 (Box Volume 2 (A-436))
    - Connecticut River Watershed Council (3rd Annual "River Ramble"), East Haddam, 1962 September 29 (Box Volume 2 (A-436))
    - Connecticut Safety Society Conference, Hartford, 1962 June 12 (Box Volume 2 (A-436))
    - Connecticut Transportation Authority, luncheon meeting with Interstate Staff Committee (Box Volume 3 (A-437))
    - Connecticut Valley State Hospital, Middletown, 1962 April 30 (Box Volume 3 (A-437))
    - Connecticut Watershed Management Field Day, West Stafford, 1961 July 12 (Box Volume 3 (A-437))
    - Conservation Awards Program, Hartford, 1965 November 20 (Box Volume 3 (A-437))
    - Conservation Field Day, Middlefield, 1962 July 28 (Box Volume 3 (A-437))
    - Constitutional Convention Opening Session, Hartford (Box Volume 3 (A-437))
    - Constitutional Convention, Closing Session, Hartford, 1965 October 28 (Box Volume 3 (A-437))
    - 1911 Corbin Automobile, Presentation of Historic Registration Plates, Hartford, 1961 October 5 (Box Volume 3 (A-437))
    - Constitution, Signing of Proclamation, Hartford, 1965 December 30 (Box Volume 3 (A-437))
    - County Adjustors Associations, Cheshire, 1962 March 6 (Box Volume 3 (A-437))
    - CYO Communion Breakfast, Sacred Heard Church, Taftville, 1965 February 7 (Box Volume 3 (A-437))
    - Danbury Rotary Club, 1965 October 6 (Box Volume 3 (A-437))
    - Danbury State College, Commencement, 1965 June 13 (Box Volume 3 (A-437))
    - Danielson Chamber of Commerce, 1962 March 5 (Box Volume 3 (A-437))
    - Democratic State Convention, Nomination of Senator Dodd for re-election, Hartford, 1964 June 6 (Box Volume 3 (A-437))
    - Democratic Victory Dinner, Hartford, 1962 December 18 (Box Volume 3 (A-437))
    - Derby-Shelton Board of Trade, Shelton, 1962 April 9 (Box Volume 3 (A-437))
    - Detroit Speech (Detroit-Chicago trip), 1962 May 15 (Box Volume 3 (A-437))
    - Development Conference, Connecticut, Hartford, 1965 November 8 (Box Volume 3 (A-437))
    - Dexter, Ch. & Sons, Inc., Dedication of new facilities, Windsor Locks, 1962 September 26 (Box Volume 3 (A-437))
    - Education, Connecticut Association of Boards of, Hartford, 1961 September 15 (Box Volume 3 (A-437))
    - Education, Connecticut Association of Boards of, Groton, 1962 September 20 (Box Volume 3 (A-437))
    - Education, Connecticut Association of Boards of, Meriden, 1965 October 22 (Box Volume 3 (A-437))
    - Education, State Board of, Convocation, Hartford, 1962 October 9 (Box Volume 3 (A-437))
    - Education, Conference on, State Department of Education, Meriden, 1965 July 19 (Box Volume 3 (A-437))
    - Electric Boat Company, Keel-laying for Polaris Submarine, Groton, 1961 October 2 (Box Volume 3 (A-437))
    - Electrical Engineers, American Institute of, Northford, 1961 May 17 (Box Volume 3 (A-437))
    - Emanuel Synagogue, 120th Anniversary of B'nai B'rith, Hartford, 1963 December 20 (Box Volume 3 (A-437))
    - Enfield Manor Housing Project, Thompsonville, 1964 September 25 (Box Volume 3 (A-437))
    - Equal Employment Opportunity Plan, Breakfast meeting at Executive Residence, 1965 June 24 (Box Volume 3 (A-437))
    - Equal Employment Opportunity, Connecticut Council for, Hartford, 1965 November 16 (Box Volume 3 (A-437))
    - Fairfield Democratic Town Committee, Fairfield, 1965 October 30 (Box Volume 3 (A-437))
    - Farmington, Dedication of Yodkins-Morin Memorial Park, 1965 October 7 (Box Volume 3 (A-437))
    - Federated Women's Clubs, Hartford, 1963 September 16 (Box Volume 3 (A-437))
    - Federation of Democratic Women's Clubs, Hartford, 1965 September 29 (Box Volume 3 (A-437))
    - Firemen's Association, State, Bethel, 1961 August 19 (Box Volume 3 (A-437))
    - Forest and Park Association, Connecticut, Hartford, 1964 April 4 (Box Volume 3 (A-437))
    - Future Farmers of America, 30th Annual Convention, Berlin, 1962 July 16 (Box Volume 3 (A-437))
    - General Assembly, Governor's Inaugural Message, 1961 January 24 (Box Volume 4 (A-438))
    - General Assembly, Governor's Budget Message, 1961 February 15 (Box Volume 4 (A-438))
    - General Assembly, Governor's Adjournment Message, 1961 June 7 (Box Volume 4 (A-438))
    - General Assembly, Governor's Inaugural Message, 1963 January 9 (Box Volume 4 (A-438))
    - General Assembly, Governor's Budget Message, 1963 February 14 (Box Volume 4 (A-438))
    - General Assembly, Governor's Message to Special Session, 1964 August 3 (Box Volume 4 (A-438))
    - General Assembly, Governor's Message to Special Session, 1964 November 10 (Box Volume 4 (A-438))
    - General Assembly, Governor's "State of the State" Message, 1965 February 2 (Box Volume 4 (A-438))
    - General Assembly, Governor's Budget Message, 1965 February 16 (Box Volume 4 (A-438))
    - General Assembly, Governor's Message to Closing Session, 1965 June 9 (Box Volume 4 (A-438))
    - Gerontology, Connecticut Society of, speech delivered by Lt. Gov. Armentano, 1961 October 28 (Box Volume 5 (A-439))
    - Gerontology, Connecticut Society of, speech delivered by Mrs. Grasso, Storrs, 1963 October 15 (Box Volume 5 (A-439))
    - Governor's Conference on Children and Youth, New Haven, 1962 April 5 (Box Volume 5 (A-439))
    - Governor's Conference on Children and Youth, Storrs, 1964 April 8 (Box Volume 5 (A-439))
    - Governor's Conference on Interregional Planning, Hartford, 1964 July 1 (Box Volume 5 (A-439))
    - Governor's Conference on Recreation, Hartford, 1961 October 24 (Box Volume 5 (A-439))
    - Governor's Conference on Recreation, Hartford, 1962 October 18 (Box Volume 5 (A-439))
    - Governor's Conference on Recreation, Hartford, 1963 October 29 (Box Volume 5 (A-439))
    - Governor's Conference on Recreation, Hartford, 1964 October 1 (Box Volume 5 (A-439))
    - Governor's Conference on Recreation, Hartford, 1965 October 19 (Box Volume 5 (A-439))
    - Governor's Conference, National, Workshop on Transportation Problems, Hershey, Pennsylvania, 1962 July 3 (Box Volume 5 (A-439))
    - Governor's Prayer Breakfast, Rhode Island, Providence, R.I., 1965 April 12 (Box Volume 5 (A-439))
    - Greenwich Safety Council, Grand Award Presentation Luncheon, Greenwich, 1965 December 3 (Box Volume 5 (A-439))
    - Hall Meadow Brook Dam, Torrington, 1961 May 15 (Box Volume 5 (A-439))
    - Hall Meadow Brook Dam & Reservoir, Dedication Ceremonies, Torrington, 1962 May 21 (Box Volume 5 (A-439))
    - Hartford Chamber of Commerce, 1961 October 13 (Box Volume 5 (A-439))
    - Hartford High School, Presentation of Thomas J. Quirk Award, 1961 March 2 (Box Volume 5 (A-439))
    - Hibernians, Ancient Order of, Stamford, 1965 October 23 (Box Volume 5 (A-439))
    - Highway Users Conference, Hartford, 1965 April 27 (Box Volume 5 (A-439))
    - Holy Innocents Guild, Hartford, 1962 May 10 (Box Volume 5 (A-439))
    - Home Builders Association, Hartford, 1962 September 27 (Box Volume 5 (A-439))